SLAH CHEBIL

Manouba, Tunisia (+216) 54369281 • sleh.chebil.sc@gmail.com • /in/slah-chebil

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Meticulous and motivated fullStack developer with 3 years of experience. Effective and self-managed during independent projects, as well as collaborating as part of a productive team. Now looking for new and challenging fullStack position where I can embrace my skills while continuing to develop my expertise.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: TS, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Java, Bash, SQL

Miscellaneous: ReactJs, Angular, Rxjs, Redux, NodeJs, NestJs, GraphQL, TanStack, Tailwind,

ChakraUI, Lerna

Jest, Vitest

Docker, Git, Gitlab, CI/CD

EXPERIENCE

FullStack Developer

Aug 2022 - Present Sousse, Tunisia

Proxym GROUPE

Dukhan Bank

- Revamped the prepaid card feature, enhancing user experience through improved functionality, security measures, and seamless integration with the existing banking infrastructure.
- Implemented an OCR to automate the extraction and validation of cheque scanner serial numbers, increasing accuracy and efficiency in cheque processing.
- Managed code versioning and continuous integration with GitLab and deployment to staging and production servers.
- Developed and launched a real-time payment transfer feature and implemented an alias beneficiary management system.
- Improved SonarQube report and fixed bugs.
- Integrated push provisioning for the Google Pay SDK, enabling secure and instant digital card issuance and management, including a card spend dashboard.

Angular | Rxjs | Ngrx | Cordova | Mobile First Platform | Java | TypeScript | Boostrap | Git/Gitlab | ClickUp

Trainee Platform

Development of a platform specialized in the recruitment of interns:

- Implementation of a Monorepos architecture.
- Perform code reviews and disseminate development best practices.
- Engineered a dynamic front-end using ReactJs and ChakraUI, integrated JavaScript modules like ReduxToolkit and Formik with Yup validation, and optimized API interactions using GraphQL.
- Managed code versioning and continuous integration with GitLab.
- Development of skills and potential assessment modules

• Allocating work to subordinates, and adhering to the timetable to achieve deadlines.

ReactJs | Redux | Nx | Saga | ChakraUl | NestJs | Vitest | Prisma | TS | PostgreSQL | Husky | Git/Gitlab

Frontend Developer - Internship

Oct 2021 – Dec 2021 Tunis, Tunisia

Development of a platform for project management:

- Fix UI and performance problems.
- Development of rebaseline feature and accounts.

ReactJs | Context | React Query | ChartJS | Bootstrap | TS | Python | Flask | Git/Github

Frontend Developer - Internship

Jun 2021 – Aug 2021

Belgrade, Serbia

MasterBox

Hostensia

- Designed and implemented a free trial feature.
- Improve SEO conversion rate using Semrush.
- Fix some UI issues and change the landing page.

WordPress | MemberPress | Css | Elementor | WooCommerce

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION

Bachelor in Computer Science, ISSIM, Tunisia

Aug 2019 - Sep 2022

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals

LANGUAGES

Arabic Native or bilingual proficiency

English Full professional proficiency

French Professional working proficiency